onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
Mikage Shrine
（奈々生(ななみ)）
社に戻って２日目
It's the second day I've been back at the shrine.
I've felt kind of weird ever since yesterday.
昨日から私は変だ
Morning, Nanami.
（巴衛(ともえ)）
おはよう 奈々生
What's wrong? Your face is red—
どうした 顔が赤…
No, it's not!
（奈々生）
赤くないわ！
こんなはずじゃないのに
This wasn't how it was supposed to be.
あれから 私ばかりドキドキして
Ever since then, I've been alone
here with my heart in my throat.
何だ しょうゆか？
What is it?
Need soy sauce?
（奈々生）
いいえ
No, thanks.
It kind of ticks me off.
ちょっと むかつきます
He's a fox, after all, right?
相手は きつねだもんね
平常心 平常心 平常心
Stay cool. Stay cool. Stay cool.
（巴衛）
やはり お前―
As I suspected, you...
have a fever.
熱があるではないか
Huh?
No way. 39.8 degrees?
うそ 39度８分？
（虎徹(こてつ)）
何という高熱！
What a high temperature!
（鬼切(おにきり)）
学校は お休みください　奈々生様
Please stay home from school, Lady Nanami!
I'll be fine. This is nothing.
大丈夫 これくらい
Besides, my attendance record is bad enough as it is.
それに 出席率が崖っぷちなの
If I miss any more days, I'll have to repeat the year.
これ以上 休んだら 留年しちゃう
M-Master Tomoe, please get Lady Nanami!
（虎徹）
と… 巴衛殿　奈々生様を！
Let me go.
（奈々生）
うーん 離して
I cannot allow you to go in your condition.
こんな体では 行かせられないな
This is a good opportunity.
よい機会だ　学校など
しばらく休んでいればよい
Take time off from something as unimportant as school.
Just because it's not your problem doesn't mean it's not important!
ひ… ひと事だと思って
勝手 言わないでよ！
Ah, your hand! Your hand!
ていうか 手… 手！
I'm saying this with your best interests at heart.
俺は お前のためを思って
言っているのだ
In that case, why not change yourself into Lady Nanami...
（虎徹）
それでしたら 巴衛殿が
奈々生様に化けて
...and go to school in her stead?
（鬼切）
代わりに学校へ行かれては
いかがでしょうか
What?
（奈々生）
それだわ！
That's a great idea!
And so, Momozono Nanami will be taking the liberty of skipping a turn today.
（講釈師）
というわけで―
今日の桃園(ももぞの)奈々生は
１回 お休みさせていただきます
Nanami
Skipping A Turn
So sorry about this.
Nanami
Skipping A Turn
すみません
Nanami
Skipping A Turn
The God Catches A Cold
Don't tell me Momozono is absent again today.
（磯辺(いそべ)）
桃園 今日も欠席じゃね？
There's no way she's not getting held back.
留年の足音が聞こえてくるな
つうわけで―
Anyone wanna bet that Momozono isn't coming today? Starting at 300 yen!
桃園の欠席に賭けるやつ
300円から！
（御手洗）
磯辺って 桃園のことになると
やたら盛り上がるな
Isobe, you get awfully excited when it comes to Momozono.
You sure you don't actually like her?
案外 好きなんじゃねえの？
（磯辺）
ハハッ　勘弁しろよ
日の丸弁当の桃園だぜ！
Good one, bro!
This is Momozono we're talking about here!
（磯辺）
面白ネタにしかなんねえっつうの
Making fun of her is all she's good for!
Hey.
（奈々生）おい
（磯辺）おう？
Huh?
Sorry to bother you, but I believe that is my seat.
すまないが そこは 確か私の席だ
どいてくれるか？
Would you mind moving?
Mo... Mo...
Momozono Nanami?!
桃園奈々生！
What's with that aura around her?
（御手洗）
何だ あのオーラは
桃園って あんなんだっけ
Was she always like that?
She's got flowers around her.
（磯辺）
バックに花が
心なしか 胸も でかく…
And did her boobs get bigger too?
Curse you, Nanami.
（巴衛）
奈々生のやつめ この付けは
必ず払わせてやるからな
You will pay for this.
（鞍馬(くらま)）
おはよう
Morning.
For the first time in a week...
１週間ぶり
the famous and talented pop star Kurama has returned to school.
超多忙スーパーアイドル
鞍馬様の ご登校だ
（女子生徒たち）
キャーッ！
The crow!
（巴衛）
天狗(てんぐ)！
（鞍馬）
これ ロケ土産
This is a souvenir from my shoot.
Huh? Nanami, you...
あっ？　奈々生 お前…
You've become more womanly since the last time I saw you.
ちょっと見ない間に
女らしくなってるじゃないか
Nice rack.
胸とか
Foolish crow.
（巴衛）
まぬけな 天狗め
俺の変化の術は完璧だ
My transformation spell is perfect.
School will be a breeze.
学校など 楽勝だな
What?!
何！　きつねが転入？
The fox transferred in?!
（男子生徒１）
うん 女子が大騒ぎしてたよな
Yeah, all the girls were freaking out about it too.
（男子生徒２）
今日は 病欠らしいけど
I think he's out sick today, though.
でも 俺 鞍馬君のほうが
かっこいいと思うな
But I think you're cooler, Kurama.
I made copies of my notes from
Japanese class. If you want them...
これ 現国のコピー　よかったら…
Seriously? Dammit.
（鞍馬）
マジかよ くそ！
I swear, I go away for a week,
and the whole school falls apart.
仕事で空けてた間に
そんなことになっていたとは
きつねのいぬ間に 奈々生との仲を
深めるつもりだったが…
I had planned on growing closer to Nanami in the fox's absence, but...
急いだほうが よさそうだな
Apparently, I don't have much time to waste.
Okay, next page.
じゃあ ネクストページ
ヘッドからリードしてくれ
Read from the top, please.
Summarizing
Prose
プリーズ ミス桃園
Miss Momozono.
（巴衛）
何だ この文字は
What the hell is this writing?
What's wrong, Miss Momozono? Please read it quickly.
（教師）
どうした ミス桃園
早く読みなさい
フッ　先生　奈々生は病み上がりで
大きい声が出ないんです
Sir.
Nanami's been sick, so she can't speak very loudly.
I'll read instead.
代わりに俺が
"All night their course lay through intricate defiles and over irregular and rock-strewn paths.
All night their course―
lay through
intricate defiles―
and over irregular and
rock-strewn paths.
More than once they lost their way, but Hope's intimate knowledge of the mountains..."
More than once
they lost their way…
Kurama's always so cool!
（女子生徒１）
さすがは鞍馬様
His pronunciation is beyond beautiful!
（女子生徒２）
発音 美しすぎる
How's that, Nanami?
（鞍馬）
どうだ 奈々生
あれ？
Huh?
Radiant in the sun
Music Room
（生徒たち）♪ 太陽に輝く…
（講釈師）２限目
Second period.
（生徒たち）
♪ 純白のウイング
With wings of purest white
はい ストップ 桃園さん
Okay, stop. Momozono.
あなただけ 音が外れているわ
もう一度 歌って
You're the only one who's out of tune. Please sing it again.
Radiant in the sun
そこが ちょっと駄目ね
That part isn't working quite right.
I have an idea, though.
じゃあ ここは―
プロの歌手に
お手本 見せていただこうかしら
Why don't we have a professional singer show us how it's done?
（生徒たち）キャーッ！
（鞍馬）オーケー
Okay.
（女子生徒１）
鞍馬様！
Radiant in the sun
With wings of purest white
In the embrace of joyous rapture
I soar in euphoria
Hallelujah!
All is within this song
Kiss me, kiss you
Kurama is singing live! I could just die!
（女子生徒２）
鞍馬様の生歌 私 もう死んでもいい
Paradise!
Wow. And it's supposed to be a choral piece.
すっげえ　合唱曲なのに
（鞍馬）
フッ　聴きほれたか 奈々生
Shadow... Die...
Did you find my singing mesmerizing, Nanami?
Uh... What?
あれ… あれ？
Nanami.
（鞍馬）
奈々生
What's wrong? You seem like you're in a bad mood today.
どうした
今日は ご機嫌 斜めだな
If something's bothering you, you can talk to me about it—
悩み事があるなら
相談に乗ってあげる…
I will say this only once.
貴様に一つだけ言っておく
You suck. Do not follow me around.
邪魔だ
（奈々生）私に付きまとうな
（鞍馬）えっ？
Huh?
お前が欲しいのは
この心臓なのだろう
I know you are after my heart quite literally,
for that is the way to obtain my status as a god.
私の神籍を狙っているのは
知っている　無駄なことだ
So back off.
Oh, man. So that's what you've been agonizing about.
参ったな
それで ずっと悩んでたのか
I'm sorry for not noticing.
悪かったよ 気付かなくて
But you've got it all wrong.
だが 誤解だ
（女子生徒１）
く… 鞍馬様！
K-Kurama?!
Hand! Hand! Hand!
（女子生徒２）
手… 手… 手！
What I really want...
俺が本当に欲しいのは 君のハート
is your love.
（女子生徒たち）
キャーッ！
Ouch!
（鞍馬）
アウチ！
Touch me again and you die!
次 触ったら 殺す
I can't believe you hit me in the face.
ていうか お前 顔を…
Nanami.
奈々生
これは まじな話なんだけど―
In all seriousness, though,
the miasma in the air at this school has grown heavier than before.
この学校の しょう気が
以前より濃くなってる
Try not to go into dark spaces by yourself.
あまり １人で暗い所に行くなよ
Miasma?
（巴衛）
しょう気…
Hm... There is definitely a heavier presence than before.
ふーん 確かに 以前より影が濃い
Darkness is the entrance to the world over yonder.
暗闇は あちら側への入り口
The miasma must mean that an entrance has opened up nearby.
この しょう気
どこかで入り口が開いたか
あの 天狗も
ただのまぬけじゃなかったらしいな
Apparently, the crow isn't as asinine as I thought.
Girls' Locker Room
Ami, hurry up or it's going to start!
（ケイ）
あみ 早くしないと始まるよ
Wait just a sec! I can't find my headband!
（あみ）
待って！
鉢巻きが見当たらないの
I know I left it here...
ここに置いてたのに
（ケイ）
とろいんだから　先 行くよ
You're so slow. I'm going on ahead.
Kei! Don't turn the lights out!
（あみ）
ケイちゃん 電気 消さないでよ
真っ暗で 何も見えない
It's totally dark, and I can't see anything!
Kei?
ケイちゃん？
Oh, no, I'm all alone.
やだ １人になっちゃった
We're in the basement, so when the door closes, you don't get any light in here.
ここ 地下だから
ドア閉めると光が入らないのに
ああん ケイちゃんの ばか
Kei, you jerk!
Who's a cute, cute little girl?
（ペロン妖怪）
かわいい かわいい女の子
甘い甘い あめの味
Does she have the sweet, sweet taste of candy?
What flavor are you?
お前は どんな味？
What?
Lick.
（ペロン妖怪）
ペロン
Strawberry flavor!
いちご味
（あみ）
キャーッ！　誰か！
Help!
I've been looking for you, girl from Class 2.
捜したぞ　２組女子
Mo...
も… 桃園さん！
お化けが お化けが出たの
Momozono! A ghost!
There was a ghost!
It licked my face!
あみの顔を ぺろんって なめたの
I know.
分かっている
It's a visitor from over yonder.
あちら側からの来客だ
お前は 先に授業に行け
You go on ahead to class.
What about you?
桃園さんは？
Finish some business in here.
（奈々生）私は 用を済ませる
（あみ）でも…
But...
Go. You're in the way.
行け 邪魔だ
（あみ）ああ…
（ケイ）あみ もう先生 来てるよ
Ami!
The teacher's here already!
Kei!
（あみ）
ケイちゃ～ん！
（ケイ）
ったく とろいんだから
Sheesh, you're so slow.
You and Momozono are the only ones who haven't shown up yet.
あんたと桃園さんだけだよ
まだ来てないのは
Did you see Momozono in the locker room?
更衣室で
桃園さん 見かけなかった？
ケイちゃん…
Kei...
Go on without me!
（あみ）先 行ってて～！
（ケイ）えっ？　あみ？
What? Ami?
I like this place.
（ペロン妖怪）
俺 ここ好き
Lots of girls come here and take off their clothes.
女の子 たくさん やって来て
脱いでくれる
I just watched them. I did nothing wrong.
俺 それ見てただけ 悪くない
S-So...
（ペロン妖怪）
だ… だから 燃やさないで
Please don't burn me!
A perverted low-level spirit.
（巴衛）
痴漢まがいの低級妖怪め
Nothing that merits my personal attention, but...
俺が手を下すまでもないのだが
奈々生のために―
For Nanami...
I must eliminate all future problems when I can.
後々の面倒事は
片付けておかねばな
What a bother.
やれやれだ
桃園さん！
Momozono!
Lick!
ペロン
お前 味しない　おいしくない
You have no flavor! You're not tasty!
Hold it!
（奈々生）待て！
（ペロン妖怪）お前 嫌い
I hate you!
Strawberry flavor!
いちご味！
Lick!
ペロ…
That's as far as you go.
そこまで
あっ 鞍馬君
Kurama?
I told you to stay away from
dark places, didn't I, Nanami?
だから 暗い所に行くなって
言っただろう？　奈々生
It hurts... It hurts...
（ペロン妖怪）
痛い痛い
（奈々生）鞍馬
（ペロン妖怪）あっ
Kurama, take that girl and go outside!
（奈々生）
その娘を連れて 外へ出ていろ！
あ… あの 鞍馬君 今のって一体…
Uh, so do you know what in the world that thing is?
Don't worry. You better hurry up and get to class.
大丈夫
早く授業に行ったほうがいいよ
But Momozono is...
でも 桃園さんが…
Can what happened today be a secret?
今日のことは
僕らだけの秘密にしとこう
You'll promise me that, won't you?
約束してくれるよね
S-Sure...
I'm coming in.
入るぞ
What happened to that spirit?
さっきの妖怪は？
逃がしてやったのか
You let it go?
Well, I guess that's fine.
まあ いいけど 気を付けろよ
But be careful.
俺は きつねみたいに―
Unlike the fox, it's not as if I can always be by your side to protect you,
いつでも そばで守ってあげられる
わけじゃないから
so don't do anything reckless when he's not around.
あいつのいないときは
むちゃすんな
Then starting tomorrow, I must have Tomoe come.
では 明日から
巴衛に出てきてもらわねばな
You can have it.
（奈々生）
やる
Next part coming right up after these messages!
right up
Next part coming
（講釈師）
続きは このあと すぐ
right up
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
This is a softshell turtle that was caught just earlier!
（虎徹）
先ほど取ったばかりの
すっぽんでございます
Partaking of softshell turtle stew is
sure to cure Lady Nanami of her cold!
（鬼切）
すっぽん鍋を食せば
奈々生様の お風邪も治りましょう
Nanami, you eat turtles and stuff? You have a weird diet.
（瑞希(みずき)）
奈々生ちゃん
亀とか食べちゃうの？　悪食(あくじき)
I have no idea how to prepare a turtle.
僕 亀の さばきかたなんて
知らないよ
More like...
ていうか どうして
瑞希が うちの台所にいるの？
What are you doing in our kitchen, Mizuki?!
What? I heard that Tomoe wouldn't be here today,
えっ？　今日は
巴衛君がいないって聞いてね
so I came to see you.
奈々生ちゃんに会いに来たんだ
And then these guys asked me to make lunch.
そしたら 彼らに昼食を頼まれて…
That hurts!
痛い！
Oh, the softshell turtle bit Master Mizuki's finger!
（虎徹）
すっぽんが瑞希殿の指に…
（鬼切）
水じゃ！
Get water!
（講釈師）
巴衛が奈々生に化けて
学校へ行っているころ―
While Tomoe was at school disguised as Nanami,
ヨノモリ社の神使 瑞希が―
Mizuki, the familiar of the Yonomori Shrine, was visiting Nanami.
奈々生の元に
訪ねてきておりました
えーっ！
巴衛君が女装して学校に？
What?!
Tomoe cross-dressed as you and went to school?
I'm more concerned about the turtle! Put it in the pot and you die!
ていうか そこ
亀 まんま鍋に入れたら殴るよ
Escape-Proof
（瑞希）
奈々生ちゃんの言霊縛りって
強烈なんだね
I guess your Sacred Word Binding must be powerful.
I didn't order him to do it.
（奈々生）
そんなの使わないよ
お願いして行ってもらったの
I asked him to go, and he did.
（瑞希）
お願いね
You asked him, huh?
Tomoe must be putting on quite the innocent act around you.
巴衛君って 君の前では
相当 猫かぶってるんだな
何よ それ
What's that supposed to mean?
彼は もともと 野狐(やこ)だからね
He was a wild fox to begin with,
so as his lady and mistress,
you have to lead him with a firm hand.
主人の君が
しっかり かじ取りをしないと
Mizuki, I don't talk appreciate you talking about Tomoe like that.
瑞希　そんなふうに巴衛のこと
言わないで
He doesn't deserve to be judged on his looks or where he came from.
見かけとか生まれとかで
勝手に判断してほしくない
Because I spend time with him, and I know him best.
一緒にいる私が いちばん
巴衛のこと分かってるから
It's easy to get the wrong idea about him,
誤解されやすいやつだけど
優しいところもあるんだよ
but he's got a gentle side to him too.
You really are...
（瑞希）
やっぱり…
totally taken in by him, Nanami.
丸め込まれちゃってるね
奈々生ちゃん
What?
さすが 巴衛君と言うべきか
神使は神の しもべなのに―
His abilities are stronger than I thought.
Familiars are supposed to serve gods,
but it appears you are the one who's been tamed instead.
飼いならされているのは
むしろ君のようにも見える
油断してると
あの獣に 寝首をかかれちゃうよ
If you let your guard down,
that beast will kill you in your sleep.
And I told you Tomoe isn't like that!
だから
巴衛は そんなんじゃないってば！
ハァー 頑固だな 奈々生ちゃんも
You're so stubborn, Nanami.
どっちが！
Look who's talking!
Then you should go take a peek with your own eyes.
じゃあ
その目で のぞいてみるといい
And see Tomoe's true colors.
巴衛君の本性を
Master Mizuki, what is this incense burner?
（虎徹）
瑞希殿 この香炉は？
うん これは 時廻(ときまわ)りの香炉
Oh, this is a time-wending incense burner.
魂を過去へ運ぶ神具だよ
It's a votive object that transports the soul to the past.
君が生まれる ずっと昔
Far in the past, before you were born.
There, you'll find a Tomoe you may not even recognize.
そこに 君の知らない巴衛君がいる
How could I not recognize Tomoe?
（奈々生）
私の知らない巴衛
Lady Nanami?
（鬼切･虎徹）
奈々生様？
She's fine.
（瑞希）
大丈夫
She's on her way now.
奈々生ちゃんには 少しだけ
時のはざまで遊んでもらおう
Off to have fun in the crevices of time.
Go take a peek.
のぞいてきてごらん
君の生まれる ずっと昔
Far into the past, before you were born.
Discover a Tomoe from before he met you.
君と出会う前の巴衛君を
Ow...
（奈々生）
痛…
Wait... Tomoe's true colors?
（奈々生）
ちょっと 巴衛の本性って
一体 何がどうなってるのよ
What in the world is going on here?
Huh?
あれ？
When did my hands get so tiny?
私 こんなに手 小さかったっけ？
And my clothes...
服も髪も…
And my hair...
これは…
This...
isn't my body!
別人の体？
Oh, yeah! This must be the world inside my dreams.
そっか 夢の中なんだ
ここは きっと
（男の子）
う… 痛いよ
It hurts...
痛いよ
A child...
（奈々生）
子供
What's wrong?
僕 どうしたの？
Miss, you can't go back to the village.
お姉ちゃん 村に戻っちゃ駄目だ
Those spirit bastards... attacked and...
妖怪のやつらが攻めてきて
Spirits?
（奈々生）
妖怪？
Akura-oh is looking for you.
悪羅王(あくらおう)が
お姉ちゃんのことを捜してる
I ran away as fast as I could, but...
僕 必死で逃げてきたけど―
みんな あいつに…
That bastard got everyone...
Akura-oh? A spirit is looking for me?
（奈々生）
悪羅王？　妖怪が私を？
Is this a dream?
これは夢なの？
近くに空き家があって助かった
Lucky for us this empty house was nearby.
It might be rundown, but it's still shelter.
ぼろだけど 雨なら しのげるわ
随分ぬれちゃったね
We got pretty drenched, huh?
I have to treat his wound.
傷の手当てをしなきゃ
Who could do this to a child?
子供に
こんな ひどいけが させるなんて
（男の子）
でも 僕 ついてたよ
I'm the lucky one.
Who would've guessed you'd be out of the village working the fields?
お姉ちゃんが畑仕事で
偶然 村を留守にしててさ
こんな上玉の生娘
悪羅王様が見逃すはずないものね
A fine virgin like you...
There's no way Lord Akura-oh would pass up that!
He takes every prey of any value away from us, after all.
めぼしい獲物は
みんな取り上げられちまうからな
No way! A spirit?!
（奈々生）
うそ 妖怪？
Don't worry. I'll devour you long before Lord Akura-oh finds us.
（妖怪）
悪羅王様に見つかる前に―
俺が おいしく頂いてやるよ
Someone!
（奈々生）
誰か！
L-Lord Tomoe...
と… 巴衛様
That was foxfire.
（奈々生）
きつね火
Trash always does burn well.
（巴衛）
くずは よく燃える
A village girl?
村の娘か？
Tomoe...
（奈々生）
巴衛
True, you are quite a fine specimen for someone from a tiny hamlet.
確かに ちっぽけな集落の
人間にしては―
なかなか良い玉だ
（奈々生）
巴衛？
Tomoe?
声もいい
Lovely voice.
Cry out for me, human.
鳴いてみろ 人間
This isn't...
（奈々生）
巴衛じゃ… 巴衛じゃない
This isn't Tomoe!
Who... are you?
誰よ あんた
Tomoe!
（悪羅王）
巴衛！
Tomoe...
（悪羅王）
巴衛 いないと思ったら
こんな所で油 売ってたのかよ
You disappear on me for what?
A rundown shack in the woods?
Someone's here! This is my chance to get away!
（奈々生）
誰か来た 今のうちに逃げなきゃ
（巴衛）
雨宿りだ　ぬれたくないからな
Shelter from the rain. I do not wish to get wet.
You're not very good company.
（悪羅王）
つきあい悪(わり)いな
I came because I heard there was a beauty here,
but the village only had old hags and ugly broads.
美人がいるって
聞いてきたのに―
村には
ばばあと しこめしかいねえ
A lot of them slipped through the cracks, though.
パラパラ逃げたやつも多いからな
交じって どっか行っちまったか
I suppose she must've slipped away with them.
A little girl gave you the slip?
小娘にまで逃げられるとは
焼きが回ったな 悪羅王
You are losing your touch, Akura-oh.
（悪羅王）
ヘッ　お前
この辺で 若い娘 見なかったか？
Did you happen to see a young girl around here?
雪路(ゆきじ)って女なんだが
They call her Yukiji.
No idea.
さあ
（瑞希）
彼は もともと野狐だからね
He was a wild fox to begin with, so if you let your guard down...
油断してると…
He's wrong.
（奈々生）
違う！
...that beast will kill you in your sleep.
（瑞希）
寝首をかかれるよ
He's wrong!
（奈々生）
違う！
そっか これは きっと夢なんだ
That's right. This must be a dream.
（瑞希）
奈々生ちゃん
Nanami.
You were gone for an awfully long time.
随分 長く 飛んでたね
Where am I?
ここは？
君の社だよ
Your shrine.
Lady Nanami, we were worried
because you took so long to awaken!
（鬼切）
奈々生様
お目覚めが遅いので 心配しました
I'm exhausted.
体が重い　私 寝てたの？
Wasn't I sleeping?
No, I sent your soul into the past.
いや 君の魂を
過去の時流に送ったんだ
What you saw was the world of
the past that leads to our present.
君が見たのは
現実とリンクする過去の世界
Did you meet Tomoe by chance?
巴衛君に会えた？
I didn't see him.
（奈々生）
会えなかった
（巴衛）
誰に会えなかったって？
Who...
were you not able to see?
Why is there a snake loitering in the shrine?
どうして 蛇男が ここにいる
Wow, Tomoe, welcome home!
（瑞希）
ハハハ… 巴衛君 おかえりなさい
学校 楽しかった？
Did you have fun at school?
What the hell are you doing here?
貴様 ここで何をしている
奈々生に何をしてたのだ
What were you doing to Nanami?
エヘヘッ ひ･み･つ
I can't tell you.
Leave!
（巴衛）帰れ！
（瑞希）あー！
That damn snake!
あの蛇野郎 なぜ 社に入れたのだ
Why did you let him into the shrine?!
We had thought to serve softshell turtle stew to Lady Nanami.
（鬼切）
奈々生様に すっぽん鍋をと
What does a stew have to do with him?!
鍋と あいつと どう関係がある！
奈々生
Nanami.
（巴衛）
熱は―
You still...
have a bit of a fever.
少しある
I will make you something for it.
何か作ってやるから
寝ているといい
so stay in bed.
（奈々生）
この手だ
That's the touch I know.
The gentle touch of Tomoe's hand.
ah ah ah ah
優しい巴衛の手
Okay.
ah ah ah ah
What is the matter? Did Mizuki do something to you?!
（巴衛）
どうした　瑞希に何かされたのか
ah ah ah ah
怖い夢を見ただけだよ
I just had a nightmare.
だから 大丈夫　ありがとう
I'll be okay, though.
ah ah ah ah
Thank you.
私の知ってる巴衛
この人でよかった
I'm so glad that this is the Tomoe I know.
ah ah ah ah
By the way, what about you? How was school?
ところで
巴衛のほうは 学校どうだった？
ah ah ah ah
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
ah ah ah ah
kamisama mou osoi
God, it's too late for me
ano ko wa...
Because she's...
Preview
Tomoe is pretty comfortable with life at school.
（講釈師）
巴衛も すっかり板についてきた
スクールライフ
Touku sora ni
gone off into the distant sky
He's very popular among the female students.
女子生徒からは モッテモテ！
Kieta no sa
and disappeared
Even Nanami's heart tends to race very quickly.
奈々生も 巴衛が気になって
ドッキドキ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah
This is the time to work up the
courage to take a step forward.
ここは 勇気を出して
一歩前へ踏み出しますぞ
Sayonara baby
Farewell, baby
Next time, "The God Asks A Boy Out On A Date."
次回「神様、デートに誘う」
The God Asks A Boy Out On A Date
Goodbye, goodbye
Come on. Let's go to the aquarium together.
ねえ 一緒に水族館 行こう